Hands free is closed I am Atul Mohan
welcome you again today we will see
that whether Maggi is made or not,
whether dinner is made or not,
two wheeler motor third party insurance will be done in two minutes in Repeat NET
In this video we have
shown the product of ICICI Lombard
but if you buy
two wheeler third party insurance policy of any insurance company then
it will be done in two and a half minutes along with this
we
thank the management of ICICI Lombard
who helped us in making this video at
this time special income incentive
program has been launched this is the opportunity for those who are
new and satisfied with their lives to
understand this easiest and simplest product and increase their income
[Music]
Welcome to this video in which
we will tell you about the steps of booking a two wheeler third party policy
Come to the Digital Seva Portal home page and
click on the Insurance option
Type ICICI Lombard in the search option Click on the ICICI Lombard icon
Get to the Life Partner home page
i.e. ICICI Lombard homepage right next to the home page  On the
right side you will
find our product options. Click on the How to
WTP icon to buy a third party bike policy.
Click on Renew Existing and Fairness and then
click on Grateful for Plan Screen One
Registration Details
After reaching the How to WTP page,
enter your customer's vehicle registration number and
click on Get It Now tap to get complete vehicle details. Check the
model, make, engine and
chassis number with your RC shown on the page
Screen Two Details The cover has already been
removed from the premium rate and TPD
is prohibited up to 6000 Previous
policy details have already been
fixed with No option. Click
on the orange Get button to view the premium Rs 828
This screen will show Customer Details
Click on the blue Create New Customer button to enter customer details Enter the house
name, address, pin code, email ID and phone number
After entering the customer details, tap
on the orange Get Proposal button to view the proposal number generated with premium Rs 828  Click on it. On the bottom right corner of the page,
you will find Buy Policy option in blue color.
Click on it to go to CSC Wallet payment page.
See the screen for Policy PDF.
After entering your CSC password and Wallet PIN,
wait for some time. You will reach a page
where you will see your policy number
and an option to view your customer's policy
PDF.